// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: "Python is an",
  answer: "All the above",
  options: [
    " interpreted, high-level, general-purpose programming language",
    "object-oriented programming language",
    "procedural, functional, structured, and reflective programming language",
    "All the above"
  ]
},



{
  numb: 2,
  question: " To shuffle the list say mylist, what function do we use ?",
  answer: "random.shuffle(mylist)",
  options: [
    "random.shuffleList(mylist)",
    "mylist.shuffle()",
    "shuffle(mylist)",
    "random.shuffle(mylist)"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 3,
  question: "What is the output of the following program ?mylist = [10, 20, 5, 30, 15] print(mylist[:-1])",
  answer: "[10, 20, 5, 30]",
  options: [
    "[10, 20, 5, 30]",
    "[10, 20, 5, 30, 15]",
    "[15, 20, 5, 30, 10",
    "Error"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 4,
  question: "What will be the output produced by following program ? mylist = [10, 20, 5, 30, 15] print(mylist * 2)",
  answer: "[10, 20, 5, 30, 15, 10, 20, 5, 30, 15]",
  options: [
    "[20, 30]",
    "[10,5, 30, 15]",
    "[20,10, 60, 30]",
    "[10, 20, 5, 30, 15, 10, 20, 5, 30, 15]"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 5,
  question: "Which of the following is an invalid statement ?",
  answer: " a b c = 1000 2000 3000",
  options: [
    "a_b_c = 1,000,000",
    "a,b,c = 1000, 2000, 3000",
    " a b c = 1000 2000 3000",
    "abc = 1,000,000"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 6,
  question: "Which are the advantages of functions in python ?",
  answer: "All of the Above",
  options: [
    "Reducing duplication of code",
    "Decomposing complex problems into simpler pieces",
    "Reuse of code",
    "All of the Above"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: "What is called when a function is defined inside a class ?",
  answer: "Method",
  options: [
    "Method",
    "Another function",
    "Class",
    "Module"
  ]
},
{
numb: 8,
question: "Which of the following is the use of id() function in python ?",
answer: "All of the Above",
options: [
  "Every object does not have a unique id",
  "Id returns the identity of the object",
  "All of the Above",
  "None of the above"
]
},
{
numb: 9,
question: "Which of the following refers to mathematical function ?",
answer: "sqrt()",
options: [
  "rhombus()",
  "add()",
  "rhombus()",
  "sqrt()"
]
},

{
numb: 10,
question: "Python supports the creation of anonymous functions at runtime, using a construct called",
answer: "Lambda",
options: [
  "anonymous",
  "Lambda",
  "pi",
  "None of the above"
]
},

// you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
// but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

//   {
//   numb: 6,
//   question: "Your Question is Here",
//   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
//   options: [
//     "Option 1",
//     "option 2",
//     "option 3",
//     "option 4"
//   ]
// },
];